Everything on the line. Nothing off the table.
High Rollers is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Randall Emmett.
A master thief must pull off a dangerous casino heist
when his nemesis kidnaps his lover.
Caught between rival criminals and FBI pursuit, he
risks all to save her and score big.
Mason Goddard, played by John Travolta.
Amelia Decker, played by Gina Gershon.
Shawn, played by Lukas Haas.
Anton, played by Quavo.
Link, played by Natali Yura.
Hector (as Noel G.), played by Noel Gugliemi.
High Rollers is a 2025 American action film directed by Ives, written by Chris Sivertson, and starring
John Travolta, Gina Gershon, Lukas Haas, Quavo, Danny Pardo,  Kelly Greyson, and Alex Hurt.
It is a sequel to Cash Out (2024).
The film was released on March 14, 2025.
The tone is intense.